<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"
 xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"
 xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
 <DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <LastAuthor>Yilin</LastAuthor>
  <Created>2014-10-24T18:05:00Z</Created>
  <Version>14.0</Version>
 </DocumentProperties>
 <OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <AllowPNG/>
 </OfficeDocumentSettings>
 <ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
  <WindowHeight>11220</WindowHeight>
  <WindowWidth>25600</WindowWidth>
  <WindowTopX>0</WindowTopX>
  <WindowTopY>1080</WindowTopY>
  <ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure>
  <ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows>
 </ExcelWorkbook>
 <Styles>
  <Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font/>
   <Interior/>
   <NumberFormat/>
   <Protection/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s16">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s17">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font/>
   <NumberFormat ss:Format="m/d/yyyy\ h:mm:ss"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s18">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font ss:Color="#0000D4" ss:Underline="Single"/>
  </Style>
 </Styles>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="Form Responses 1">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="4" ss:ExpandedRowCount="29" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultColumnWidth="87" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15.75">
   <Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="129" ss:Span="3"/>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Timestamp</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Short bio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Link to PDF CV</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-09T15:06:54.989</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Kaitlin Donohue</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Kaitlin Donohue is currently the Recruitment Coordinator for the College of Arts and Letters (CAL) at Stevens Institute of Technology. She performs outreach to national high school students and assists with marketing efforts for undergraduate programs in Science and Technology Studies, Music &amp; Technology, Visual Arts &amp; Technology, and the Humanities and Social Sciences. Prior to her time at Stevens, Ms. Donohue completed her graduate studies at Georgetown University in Biohazardous Threat Agents and Emerging Infectious Diseases. She subsequently spent time working as a Senior Biosurety Analyst at a Government contractor in the Washington, D.C. area. Kaitlin’s time in this role resulted in opportunities to gain experience in marketing, recruiting, business intelligence, and branding; newfound interests which ultimately led to her current position at Stevens.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/igrsjo3hukoxkuj/KAITLIN DONOHUE_Resume 10 2014.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/igrsjo3hukoxkuj/KAITLIN%20DONOHUE_Resume%2010%202014.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-12T22:23:23.071</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Yijing Mao</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name: Yijing Mao&#13;Bio: Yijing Mao is a graduate student of Business Intelligence and Analysis at Stevens Institute of Technology. She has a bachelor of Statistics from Zhongnan University of Economics and Law. Yijing has many experiences of market research and analysis by using statistic models and methods. She is interested in data visualization and graphic design except for data analysis. She also has some startup experiences and involved in vary kind of social issues and activities, such as social innovation and Startup Weekend.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/fydt4ep6ictrmc7/RESUME%2C MAO.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/fydt4ep6ictrmc7/RESUME%2C%20MAO.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-12T22:30:46.638</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ruihan Lu</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ruihan Lu is a full time student, who now majored in Business Intelligence and Analysis. She attended Stevens Institute of Technology in Autumn 2013 and majored in Applied mathematic in first semester.  Additionally, Ruihan has bachelor of Information and Computing science in China. Ruihan Lu</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">yes</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-12T23:41:07.653</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Tengjiao Zhu</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Tengjiao Zhu is a graduate student at Stevens Institute of Technology. Her major is Business Intelligence and Analytics. She has a bachelor of management from Huazhong Agricultural University and a master from Renmin University of China. She has worked in Jiangsu Zhongya Sugar &amp; Wine Co., Ltd. for one month as an internship, assisting in strategizing marketing plans, and undertaking the proofreading works of marketing plans to be released. She has also worked in Jiangsu Jingjiang Municipal Economic and Informatization Commission for two months, entering and preceding collected data relating to economics and informatization. She has done two researches for her graduation thesis. The topic of the first one is “Analysis of Influence of the Rural Social Security System on Farmers' Consumption-Taking Jingjiang Jiangsu Province for Example” and the topic of the second one is “The Impacts of Education upon Non-agricultural Employment of Rural Labor Force during Urbanization Process”.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/sh/duphscv8si0s6yd/AADrYr_c3PwfTtOVHyn5LRjxa?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/sh/duphscv8si0s6yd/AADrYr_c3PwfTtOVHyn5LRjxa?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-12T23:46:09.290</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ankit Kumar Jawla</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ankit kumar Jawla was born &amp; raised in new delhi, capital of India. He is pursuing master’s of science degree in cloud computing &amp; enterprise at Stevens Institution of Technology, USA . Ankit holds a Bachelor of Technology degree in Electronics and Communication engineering from Rajasthan Technical University, India. He has worked as a Senior Executive Engineer in SIEMENS from April ’11- till Aug ’14. Ankit is having extensive experience and management skills and worked for a hi-tech multinational telecommunication company. Siemens Enterprise Communications, is a global communications software and services company. As a senior engineer he was responsible for managing turn key communications projects &amp; developing new business for the company. He has won achievers award for outstanding contribution towards business growth in the financial years 2011-12 &amp; won a excellent employee of the year award in  2012 -13. &#13;&#13;Ankit Kumar Jawla has good knowledge of cloud platforms like Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2), Amazon S3, Salesforce. He is working on a cloud based enterprise application using IDE tools &amp; languages like Eclipse, Java, XML etc. &#13;&#13;Prior to joining Siemens Ankit has also worked in Realvia as Management Trainee. Further, He has under went 4 weeks summer training with PRICOL Ltd, India where he studied about quality control test on two wheeler assemblies of clusters. In under graduation, He won chess competition at TechBloom-2009 (National Level Fest) Rajasthan, India. Ankit represented college as part of chess team and cricket team from 2006-2010. He has a certification of “Basic Concept in Multimedia” from Delhi institution of computer education.Currently He lives in Jersey city, USA. Ankit has lived in India and he speaks 3 languages (English , Hindi &amp; Punjabi) and in his spare time, he really enjoys playing chess &amp; football.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0KbNvVJXEr-U1RKa3Btc3BBTHc/view?usp=sharing"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0KbNvVJXEr-U1RKa3Btc3BBTHc/view?usp=sharing</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-13T02:04:11.327</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ning Li</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ning Li is a graduate student in Business Intelligence &amp; Analytics program of Stevens Institute of Technology. He has a bachelor of information system from University of Shanghai for Science and Technology. His research is focused on data mining and data analysis in social networks and finance. He worked in iResearch Consulting Company, Information Technology Department, Shanghai, China.  He Supervised a team  to cooperate with Financial Department to design Cashflow Analysis System of public companies. In future his objective is concentrating on financial data analysis which includes statistic learning and consulting.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=0B41CxaNxnm18T3VXNS1Ddm1KR1k&amp;usp=sharing"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=0B41CxaNxnm18T3VXNS1Ddm1KR1k&amp;usp=sharing</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-13T15:22:43.374</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ankit Kumar Jawla</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ankit kr Jawla is born &amp; brought up in New Delhi, India. He is pursuing his Master’s of Science degree in cloud computing &amp; enterprise at Stevens Institution of Technology, USA. Ankit holds a Bachelor of Technology degree in Electronics and Communication Engineering from Rajasthan Technical University, India. He has worked as a Senior Executive Engineer in SIEMENS from April ’11- till Aug ’14.As a senior engineer he was responsible for managing turnkey communications projects &amp; developing new business for the company. He has won achievers award for outstanding contribution towards business growth in the financial years 2011-12 &amp; won a excellent employee of the year award in  2012 -13. &#13;&#13;Ankit Kumar Jawla has good knowledge of cloud platforms like Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2), Amazon S3, Salesforce. He is working on a cloud based enterprise application using IDE tools &amp; languages like Eclipse, Java, XML etc. Prior to joining Siemens Ankit has also worked in Realvia as Management Trainee. Further, He underwent 4 weeks summer training with PRICOL Ltd, India. In under graduation, He won chess competition at TechBloom-2009 (National Level Fest) Rajasthan, India. Ankit represented college as part of chess team and cricket team from 2006-2010. He has a certification of “Basic Concept in Multimedia” from Delhi institution of computer education.Currently He lives in Jersey city, USA. Ankit has lived in India and he speaks 2 languages (English &amp; Hindi) and in his spare time, he really enjoys playing chess &amp; football. Further Ankit has good group dynamic knowledge, He has cohesive working skills which has made him to work efficiently in each and every company he has joined. He has always been known for his good public relationship skills and ability to pitch client.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0KbNvVJXEr-U1RKa3Btc3BBTHc/view?usp=sharing"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0KbNvVJXEr-U1RKa3Btc3BBTHc/view?usp=sharing</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-13T20:47:37.338</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Yu</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">My name is Yu Zhang.I came from China.Now I am study business intelligence &amp;analytics. I graduated from Beihang University at 2012,July.My undergraduate major  is financial  engineering.  I came USA at 2012.I studied in Language Culture Center at Houston University last year.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/8wxx0647zxx9u6c/coop-reseum 10.10.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/8wxx0647zxx9u6c/coop-reseum%2010.10.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-13T21:36:27.571</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Prasad Sonawane</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name: Prasad Sonawane Bio&#13;&#13;	Prasad Sonawane is a current MBA – Marketing student at Stevens Institute of Technology. This is his second Masters Degree from Stevens and the first being in Business Administration and Management. He did his Bachelors in Pharmacy from Pune University in India. He has held various leadership positions throughout his student life, the latest being President of the Graduate Student Council at Stevens, where he manages 22 associations and a healthy budget of $110,000 for all 4,000 graduate students on campus. He has professional experience ranging from working for start-ups to Fortune 100 companies and reporting directly to managers and all the way up to C-suite. He is passionate about leadership and strategy, and his areas of strength include market research, marketing, business development, project management, and consulting. He has headed multiple projects in CPG, Retail, IT, Finance, Banking, and Telecommunications Industries.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="http://www.prasadsonawane.com"><Data
      ss:Type="String">www.prasadsonawane.com</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T00:03:40.438</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Jeston Guy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name: Jeston Guy&#13;Bio:  Jeston is currently employed as a telephony engineer at Verizon Communication.  He is responsible for designing telephony networks to deliver high bandwidth circuits mostly to commercial customers.  To provision these circuits he will often have to deploy a multiplexer if one is not currently available.  His extended duties also include building out the FiOS network and sometimes the copper network to residential and commercial customers.  &#13;His educational background includes a bachelor of engineering and a master’s in business administration.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/sh/emy66xl3c3iuyy2/AAAUBl1VWe8xrNbZ-r32F1Xya?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/sh/emy66xl3c3iuyy2/AAAUBl1VWe8xrNbZ-r32F1Xya?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T01:41:05.909</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Subramanian Vellaiyan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name:  Subramanian Vellaiyan&#13;Bio: Subramanian Vellaiyan is a graduate student at Stevens Institute of technology pursuing Master’s in Business Intelligence and Analytics. He has a bachelor of engineering in electrical and electronics from Anna University, Chennai. Subramanian has two years of work experience in the field of data loading, business intelligence and big data. His experience was related to retail domain especially in pricing insights and retail promotions of retailers and manufacturers. He has presented a paper on efficient solar cells at PSG College of Technology during his under graduation. Subramanian’s strong foundation in Math’s and Science brought him great accolades from all his teachers back in school. He is very flexible when it comes to new technologies. His technical interest lies primarily in mathematics, quantitative aptitude and anything related to data. Also he is very much interested in setting his future career in the fraud analytics, criminal investigation, etc. Apart from technical activities, Subramanian is passionate about adventure, archaeology, world history, early human inventions, human psychology, astrology and mythological stories.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://drive.google.com/a/stevens.edu/file/d/0B2EZqMSXkmO9XzB1cUtlRXpXY0k/view"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://drive.google.com/a/stevens.edu/file/d/0B2EZqMSXkmO9XzB1cUtlRXpXY0k/view</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T10:09:57.093</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Paul Svenson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Paul Svenson is currently a Master of Science candidate in Business Intelligence and Analytics within the Howe School of Technology Management at Stevens Institute of Technology. In addition to taking courses for his degree requirements, Paul works as a Graduate Student Assistant with Stevens Offices of Graduate Admissions, guiding students through the Graduate application process. In his free time, Paul practices and bowls in tournaments with the Stevens Bowling Team, in addition to bowling in two leagues at Bowl-Rite Lanes in Union City, NJ. Paul is a Bachelor of Science in Meteorology with a concentration in Weather Risk Management and holds minors in Mathematics and Statistics. He graduated from Penn State University – University Park Campus in May 2014, receiving honors and recognition for his outstanding achievement in scholarship, experiential learning, and service to his college. During the summer of 2013, Paul worked with NOAA, a branch of the Department of Commerce, conducting research to help increase the efficiency of wind power production from wind turbines throughout the Midwestern United States. Paul presented his findings in Washington D.C. to policy makers and leaders within NOAA. Paul hopes to one day use his diverse background to help organizations solve complex business problems as they relate to a changing and unpredictable weather and climate system.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/x6o85n8ricadi9c/svenson.paul.resume.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/x6o85n8ricadi9c/svenson.paul.resume.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T12:58:31.988</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Sahil Patani</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Sahil Patani is a Graduate student pursuing his Master's in Computer Science at Stevens Institute of Technology.He intended minors are Cloud computing and Business Intelligence Analytics. He is interested in learning cloud technology and big data algorithms.He has also published two papers,one each in Cloud Computing and Data Mining.He has a strong interest in world economy and the stock markets.He began investing in the stock market at an early age of 19.Further he also has international business exposure.He has represented Success Enterprises(Pune,India) in two international conferences.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Submitted</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T13:24:01.559</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Yunjing Yao 10395675</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Yunjing YaoBio: Yunjing Yao is currently a Business Intelligence graduate student at Stevens Institute of Technology, Howe School of Technology Management. She has a bachelor of science degree of business Administration. &#13;With basic knowledge of SQL,R,SAS and  Python, she is passionate to use her data analysis skills to solve business problems.&#13;Through studies, several internship or part time job and professional working experience of a commercial bank, have gained skills in problem solving, critical thinking, multi-tasking and effective communication.&#13;She is highly self-motivated, eager to learn, confident and poised in interactions with individuals at all levels.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/wdsxjo2c9pzaohd/Josslyn_resume.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/wdsxjo2c9pzaohd/Josslyn_resume.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T14:32:06.051</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Hardick Shobhawat</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name : Hardick Shobhawat&#13;Bio: Hardick Shobhawat is a MBA candidate at Stevens Institute of Technology, Howe School of Management. He has a Bachelor of Fashion Technology from NIFT,India and Master of Science in technology Management from CEPT University, India.&#13;&#13;Recently he was part of Strategy consulting team working with Bank of New York Mellon on Risk Analytics and Disruptive technologies.&#13;&#13;After completing his undergrad Hardick started an Apparel Manufacturing unit. He has also worked with Major apparel players in India in their R&amp;D department.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/au704ppz3kcke8k/Hardick Shobhawat RESUME.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/au704ppz3kcke8k/Hardick%20Shobhawat%20RESUME.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T14:41:17.482</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Yilin Wei</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name: Yilin Wei&#13;Bio: Yilin Wei is a graduate student of M.S. Business Intelligence and Analytics in Stevens Institute of Technology. She has a bachelor of business administration from Nankai University, China. She also studied finance, supply chain management and French in Rouen Business Schoole, France.&#13;Accountant internships in Nestle and Airbus strengthened Yilin’s analytic skill, and encouraged her to learn data analytics. Now her new hobby is learning SAS. Because of interest in technology industry, she choose to do a search engine optimization intern in UC Web, gaining insights into digital analysis and game industry.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/105037578/Resume-Yilin Wei.pdf"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/105037578/Resume-Yilin%20Wei.pdf</Data><Comment
      ss:Author=""><Data>Responder updated this value.</Data></Comment></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T15:11:32.880</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Nikunj Mathur</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Nikunj Mathur is originally from India and is currently in a Master’s Program in Enterprise and Cloud Computing at Stevens Institute of Technology. Before coming to Stevens he completed graduation program: B.Tech in Computer Science from Uttar Pradesh Technical University, India in 2011. He is interested in innovation and technology, and is excited by the way technology has evolved to the point that many of our practices and methods around work could change radically. &#13;Between 2011-2014, Nikunj worked as a Senior System Executive for the Cognizant Technology Solutions, India. During his tenure at CTS, Nikunj have worked for three different clients and drove the transition process for one of the client. He did intern in SAP from Gas Authority India limited (GAIL) and learnt the ways to extract meaningful information from bulk of data. He worked with charitable trust ‘Lok Kalyan Trust’ to move all their reporting, financials and student and website data to a local server,  which has helped them to improve data administration and organize data for easy reporting.&#13;Nikunj is interested in the ways cloud computing save money with pay-as-you-go model and looking for the ways a small business could adapt cloud computing.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B-m9Mc6P8sFwdzJYN0lJMzF3czA/view?usp=sharing"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B-m9Mc6P8sFwdzJYN0lJMzF3czA/view?usp=sharing</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T15:16:07.274</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">yida wang</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name:  Yida (Eddy) Wang&#13;Bio: Yida Wang is a Master Candidate at Stevens Institute of Technology, program of Business Intelligence and Analytics. He has a bachelor of engineering from Shandong University of Technology. Yida's research is focused on “big data” analysis and business intelligence. He has taken courses such as financial decision making, strategic data management, process analytics &amp; optimization, multivariate data analytics, data warehousing &amp; business intelligence, supply chain management, social network analytics and risk management methods &amp; applications. He interested in finding hidden value inside data for effective decision making and business innovation. He also interested in international trading and marketing strategy. Yida had working experience in Fraser Suites Chengdu, and participated in “young talent program” in Citibank Chengdu. Further, he enjoys being a volunteer and a basketball player.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/9fakc2cuatad39w/Yida (Eddy) Wang CV.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/9fakc2cuatad39w/Yida%20(Eddy)%20Wang%20CV.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T15:17:24.520</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Hani Safadi</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Hani Safadi is a PHD Candidate at McGill University, Desautels Faculty of Management. He has a bachelor of engineering and a master of science from McGill University. Hani's research is focused on new forms of organization and large scale collaboration enabled by information technology. His dissertation centers on open-source health information technology and open innovation communities in healthcare. He is involved in other research streams including the role of social media in social movements and leadership in online communities. Hani had worked and consulted on diverse projects including projects involving open innovation, social networks and healthcare IT. Further, he has experience in conducting quantitative and qualitative research projects with two papers under review in ISR &amp; HPT and ten North American conference publications</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="http://personal.stevens.edu/~hsafadi/Hani_Safadi_Resume.pdf"><Data
      ss:Type="String">http://personal.stevens.edu/~hsafadi/Hani_Safadi_Resume.pdf</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T16:34:51.272</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">yida wang</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name:  Yida (Eddy) Wang&#13;Bio: Yida Wang is a Master Candidate at Stevens Institute of Technology, program of Business Intelligence and Analytics. He has a bachelor of engineering from Shandong University of Technology. Yida's research is focused on “big data” analysis and business intelligence. He has taken courses such as financial decision making, strategic data management, process analytics &amp; optimization, multivariate data analytics, data warehousing &amp; business intelligence, supply chain management, social network analytics and risk management methods &amp; applications. He interested in finding hidden value inside data for effective decision making and business innovation. He also interested in international trading and marketing strategy. Yida had working experience in Fraser Suites Chengdu, and participated in “young talent program” in Citibank Chengdu. Further, he enjoys being a volunteer and a basketball player.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/4djvbwf6a9j2zm4/Yida%27s CV.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/4djvbwf6a9j2zm4/Yida%27s%20CV.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T16:41:20.035</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Yida Wang</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Name:  Yida (Eddy) Wang&#13;Bio: Yida Wang is a Master Candidate at Stevens Institute of Technology, program of Business Intelligence and Analytics. He has a bachelor of engineering from Shandong University of Technology. Yida's research is focused on “big data” analysis and business intelligence. He has taken courses such as financial decision making, strategic data management, process analytics &amp; optimization, multivariate data analytics, data warehousing &amp; business intelligence, supply chain management, social network analytics and risk management methods &amp; applications. He interested in finding hidden value inside data for effective decision making and business innovation. He also interested in international trading and marketing strategy. Yida had working experience in Fraser Suites Chengdu, and participated in “young talent program” in Citibank Chengdu. Further, he enjoys being a volunteer and a basketball player.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/4djvbwf6a9j2zm4/Yida%27s CV.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/4djvbwf6a9j2zm4/Yida%27s%20CV.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T19:19:27.754</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Joel Perez</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Joel Perez is currently a Project Manager at Kate Spade &amp; Company, a global lifestyle brand that focuses on women's apparel and accessories. Joel started at Kate Spade 4 years ago as a Business Analyst in the Warehouse and Distribution team, focusing on Supply Chain and Logistics projects. Major projects included the start-up of a 750,000 sq/ft distribution center in California. Joel later moved on to working on the Business Intelligence team, where he was instrumental in managing the teams projects, and obtaining and documenting business requirements. Prior to his work at Kate Spade, Joel spend 4 years working for K. Hovnanian Homes, a top nationally ranked home builder. There he served as a Sr. Business Analyst rolling out JD Edwards Oracle One ERP system, as well as a suite of systems to business units across the country. Joel is currently pursuing his Master’s in Information Management from Stevens Institute of Technology. He has a bachelor in Business &amp; Technology and a Project Management certificate from Stevens. Joel is a motivated self starter, with the ability to build business report, and learn quickly and on the fly with minimal guidance in a fast pace environment. He has experience managing vendors, designing technology based solutions, and enhancing processes to achieve efficiency in a variety of areas.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/jkoghr0j900318a/Joel M Perez Resume.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/jkoghr0j900318a/Joel%20M%20Perez%20Resume.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T19:41:49.900</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ruihan Lu</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Ruihan Lu is a full time student who now majored in Business Intelligence and Analysis. She attended Stevens Institute of Technology in Autumn 2013 and majored in Applied mathematic in first semester.  Additionally, Ruihan has bachelor of Information and Computing science in China.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/avu4gzabtd72s8d/Ruihan Lu%27s CV.docx?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/avu4gzabtd72s8d/Ruihan%20Lu%27s%20CV.docx?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T22:23:41.609</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Nikunj Mathur</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Nikunj Mathur is from India and is currently in a Master’s Program in Enterprise and Cloud Computing at Stevens Institute of Technology. Before joining Stevens, he completed graduation program: B.Tech in Computer Science from Uttar Pradesh Technical University, India in 2011. He is interested in innovation and technology, and is excited by the way technology simplifies otherwise complex tasks.&#13;&#13;Between 2011-2014, Nikunj worked as a Senior System Executive with Cognizant Technology Solutions (CTS), India. During his tenure at CTS, Nikunj worked for three different clients and drove the transition process for one of the client. He did his internship in SAP from Gas Authority India limited (GAIL) and learnt the ways to extract meaningful information from bulk data. He worked with charitable trust ‘Lok Kalyan Trust’ to move all their reporting, financials and student and website data to a local server,  which has helped them to improve data administration and organize data for easy reporting.&#13;&#13;Nikunj is interested in the ways cloud computing can save money with pay-as-you-go model and is looking for ways small businesses could adapt cloud computing.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0BzaWkCh5yZJaanRBZVFPUnNtS00/view?usp=sharing"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://drive.google.com/file/d/0BzaWkCh5yZJaanRBZVFPUnNtS00/view?usp=sharing</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-14T23:58:57.381</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Naman Jain</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Naman Jain is a graduate student at Stevens Institute of Technology, Wesley J. Howe School of Technology Management, where he is pursuing Masters of Science in Business Intelligence and Analytics. He received his bachelor of engineering degree in Computer Science from BIT Mesra, India. Prior to joining Stevens he worked a couple of years as a Programmer Analyst in Cognizant Technology Solutions. He has good experience in Mainframe computers, programming languages, databases and various statistical and analytical tools. He is interested in the world of big data and analytics with keen interest in data mining and network analysis.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/stkmisft2kqbsl1/CV_NAMAN.pdf?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/stkmisft2kqbsl1/CV_NAMAN.pdf?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-16T16:02:02.790</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">qiaoqi sun</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">I am a first-year BI&amp;A student of Stevens Institute of Technology. I finished my undergraduate program of Financial Engineering in Shanghai University of International Business and Economics in May this year. I am studying some programming software such as SQL, SAS, EXCEL, etc. I had interns in CITI Bank and Bank of China in Shanghai.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/fq8r603uejo33f8/Resume.doc?dl=0"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/fq8r603uejo33f8/Resume.doc?dl=0</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-20T13:19:21.619</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Dmitry Rassakhatsky</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Dmitry Rassakhatsky  a Graduate student pursuing his Master's in Business Analysis and Analytics at Stevens Institute of Technology. He has 5 years of IT consulting experience that include:&#13;- Ability to effectively solve integration problems of any complexity&#13;- Business processes optimisation, project management, reports, and optimisation of existing infrastructure&#13;- Extensive work with end-users and external contractors&#13;- Seamless integration with SAP (ECC, CRM, BW/BI) and Oracle Solutions (Business Suit, ATG)&#13;- Data transformations of any complexity (Java Mapping, XSLT, Python Transformations, Message Mappings)&#13;- Security examination and audit of the current systems.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="http://cl.ly/03381t3k0E18"><Data
      ss:Type="String">http://cl.ly/03381t3k0E18</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="15">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="DateTime">2014-10-21T09:51:27.498</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Alek Liskov</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Alek Liskov is a graduate student at Stevens Institute of Technology, working towards a Masters of Business Intelligence and Analytics degree. He graduated from East Stroudsburg University with majors in Computer Science, Applied Mathematics and Economics. He is an energetic and driven individual, with an entrepreneurial mindset, who seeks to build a career at the intersection of business and technology. He is a strong believer in the positive impact technology has on our planet and thinks analytics can help introduce great efficiencies and revolutionize the business environment.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18" ss:HRef="https://www.dropbox.com/s/3ntvtsicp85qqiq/AlekLiskov_Resume.pdf"><Data
      ss:Type="String">https://www.dropbox.com/s/3ntvtsicp85qqiq/AlekLiskov_Resume.pdf</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <Unsynced/>
   <PageLayoutZoom>0</PageLayoutZoom>
   <Selected/>
   <FreezePanes/>
   <FrozenNoSplit/>
   <SplitHorizontal>1</SplitHorizontal>
   <TopRowBottomPane>1</TopRowBottomPane>
   <ActivePane>2</ActivePane>
   <Panes>
    <Pane>
     <Number>3</Number>
    </Pane>
    <Pane>
     <Number>2</Number>
     <ActiveRow>8</ActiveRow>
     <ActiveCol>2</ActiveCol>
    </Pane>
   </Panes>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
</Workbook>
</channel>
</rss>
